谁想过2英里每小时的速度转圈会这么累?
Whoever thought walking in a circle/at two miles an hour would be draining?
有新鲜空气啊 当做运动啦
Fresh air,exercise.
事情有时候确有不好一面的
You know,some things do/have their negative sides.
我们的收入少了一半
Our income just got cut in half.
那我们在一起的时间就多一倍
And we get to spend twice/as much time together.
不止呢/要是你不在午休结束前跑去上班的话
More,if you don't leave/before your lunch hour's over.
让开
Out of my way.
我们有权利合法拦阻你15秒
We have a legal right to/hold you up for 15 seconds.
15...14
15...14,
我数一
one.
11 10
11, 10,
我还得工作的
Just trying to do my job.
别激动 再多几秒你就可以走了
Hey,relax,three more/seconds,and you can go.
你是在教训我?
Are you telling me what to do?
没事的
It's okay.
深呼吸
Just take a breath.
离我远点
Get the hell off me.
我想15秒已经过了
I think it's been 15.
你还好吧?
You okay?
天啊 Jeff!
oh,my god,jeff!
这里真是一团糟
This place is a mess.
欢迎来到无护士世界
Welcome to a world without nurses.
来 先弄好这些
Here,you can start with these.
不是我的错 护士不是我弄丢的
It's not my fault. I didn't lose nurses.
Cuddy在找你 想派你来这
Cuddy was looking for you./Said she'd send you down here.
我知道 这就是为什么我会在这
I know,that's why I'm here.
因为Cuddy还没找到你
Because Cuddy hasn't found you yet.
她就会到处去找/却不会想到我正在这躲着
She's gonna look everywhere except/the place she wants me to be.
- 嘿/- 我这有个大动脉爆开的患者
- Hey./- I've got an aortic dissection here.
那白痴有什么事?
What's with the idiot?
呃...
****
昏迷和味觉倒错史
Fainting spell and recent/history of dysgeusia.
觉得所有食物吃起来都像柠檬派
Everything tastes like/lemon meringue pie.
你想要他?
You want to take him?
不
No.
先生
Sir.
为什么你前面有两份午饭?
Why do you have two/lunches in front of you?
在这呆了两顿饭时间了
Been here for two meals.
而你还觉得高兴?
And you're happy with that?
不 我只是觉得抱怨没有用
No,I just don't see/much use in complaining.
认真的?
Seriously?
抱怨是很有用的工具
It's a very useful tool.
你可以通过抱怨使人们悲惨
Complain,you make people miserable.
他们就得按你说的去做来脱离悲惨
They do what you want to/make the misery go away.
也许你该说些什么
You probably should say something.
我可以给共事过的医生打电话--
Maybe I can call one of/the doctors I work with--
他们在尽力了
they're doing their best.
搞什么鬼?
What the hell?
我相信只是意外
I'm sure it was an accident.
他是加拿大人?
Is he canadian?
他的情况属低优先级...
uh,he's a low priority...
那他是加拿大人?
is that a yes?
- 他只是--/- 开心
- He's just--/- happy.
我必须在扩散之前遏制住它
I gotta stop this before it spreads.
你们停手
You guys are done.
可能是代谢紊乱 中毒
This could be a metabolic/disorder,toxic exposure,
舌癌转移到脑部 癫痫或多发性硬化症
carcinoma of the tongue/metastasized the brain,epilepsy,M.S.
或是流感 我们该回急诊室了
or it could be the flu,and we/should all be back in the ER
不 你们都忽略了一个大症状
no,you're ignoring the big symptom.
也许同时患了流感和教养良好?
What if we're looking at both/the flu and decent parenting?
好 你们两个都没患教养良好病
Okay,you two are perfectly healthy.
这个人不是在迎合大众
This guy wasn't pandering.
他不是一般的和善
He wasn't vanilla nice.
他的和善无任何所图 不为个人利益
He was nice without any/aspiration,personal gain.
我认为是基因缺陷
I'm thinking genetic defect.
和善是缺陷?
Niceness is a defect?
三个穴居人见一个陌生人持矛冲过来
Three cavemen see a stranger/running towards them with a spear.
一个出手相抗 一个逃跑/还有一个微笑着请他进屋吃点东西
One fights,one flees,one smiles/and invites him over for fondue.
最后这个人还没等繁衍后代就死翘翘了
That last guy didn't last/long enough to procreate.
那病人患病多久了?
And how long has the/patient been suffering?
至少在他妻子认识他之前
At least as long as/his wife has known him.
11年
11 years.
这么久都没确诊病因的几率为—
The chances of him having an/undiagnosed pathology for that long—
你在说什么?
what are you saying?
进化论是错误的?
That evolution is wrong?
我们现在在哪 21世纪的美国?
Where do you think we/are,21st-century america?
他只是说统计学也是正确的
he's saying that/statistics are true too.
世界万物符合正态分布
The world is a bell curve.
大多数人在标准差范围内
Most of us fall within/the standard deviation,
但总有例外 如果我们承认有极品混蛋
but there are outliers,and if we believe/in the existence of extreme jerkiness,
我怀疑确实有这么一个...
which I suspect that we do...
那同样也得承认有反方向的极端
then we also have to accept the/existence of the opposite extreme.
你想把这变成一项症状/你就可以理所当然地当混球
You want it to be a symptom because/then we're supposed to be jerks,
甚至不必试图对人和善
which means you don't even/have to try to be nice.
好 也许我有偏见
Okay. Maybe I'm biased.
我们来投票吧
Let's take a vote.
谁认为和善不是个症状?
Who thinks that niceness/is not a symptom?
谁认为自己的投票算数?
And who thinks that their vote counts?
你俩 去他家查毒素
You two,check out his home for toxins.
- Taub和31号.../- 31号?
- Taub and thirty-one.../- thirty-one?
抱歉 我以为倒过来你也不介意
Oh,I'm sorry,I thought that/either way was good with you.
Taub和13/做核磁共振查肿瘤 脑电图查神经损伤
Taub and thirteen,mri for/tumors and eeg for nerve damage.
验排泄物查其他病
Test whatever comes out/of him for everything else.
轴心太倾斜了
too much axis tilt.
直到拇指到球底部前别松开
Don't release until your thumb's/at the bottom of the ball.
我猜Wilson没空吧
I assume wilson was busy.
又没空
Again.
轴心没倾斜
No axis tilt.
他跟Amber在一起?
With amber?
又在一起
Again.
还是谢谢你好心邀请我
Still,it was nice of you to invite me.
很好玩
This is fun.
我不是好心
no,it wasn't.
也不好玩
No,it isn't.
我不是出于好心才邀请你
I didn't invite you to be nice.
我请你是因为/保龄不是男人独自做的两件事之一
I invited you because bowling isn't one/of the two things guys do by themselves.
另外一件呢?
What's the second thing?
用另一只手做
Other hand.
要是人们不能做到和善
if people are incapable of being nice,
那为啥创造出和善这个词?
why bother having the word?
这是和善的本体论证据
The ontological proof of niceness.
如果有这词汇 世上就一定有这东西
The existence of the word proves/the existence of the concept.
那你回家可要小心牛头怪了
Look out for those/minotaurs on your drive home.
我以为动机并不重要
And I thought motives didn't matter.
结果才重要
Only results mattered.
那你是想破坏Wilson的感情
so what are you gonna do to/screw up wilson's relationship
就不必在打保龄时听我唧唧歪歪?
so you don't have to/listen to me while you bowl?
我衷心祝福他们和他们可怜的畸形儿
I wish the best for them and/their tragically deformed children.
她擅长使坏
well,she's good at being bad.
你不一定斗得过她
You might not be able to destroy her.
只要我使出看家本领
As long as I give it my best shot.
虽败犹荣
I'm gonna hold my head high.
Cameron也有个教人难以忍受的朋友
Cameron had this one/insufferable friend.
她不会与她绝交/而我也不打算跟她们一起玩
She wasn't gonna get rid of her,and/I sure wasn't gonna join 'em.
所以我就把星期四分给她
So I just said,"see her on thursdays."
虽然不是什么让人激动的计划
I know it's not as exciting/as an exploding birthday cake,
我反正也不打算每晚都跟她一起
but,hell,I don't want to hang/out with her every night anyway.
难以置信
That's amazing.
Cameron只有一个惹人厌的朋友?
Cameron only has one/insufferable friend?
共同监护
Joint custody.
监护Wilson?
Of Wilson?
不然我们还有别的孩子?
Unless we have another love child.
搞定他
Deal with him.
他需要母爱
He needs a mother figure.
我没说你没权利跟他在一起
I'm not saying you're not/entitled to spend time with him.
我意思是我也有权
I'm just saying I'm entitled too.
他有理时我搞不定他
I don't know how to deal with/him when he's being reasonable.
这还叫有理?
this is reasonable?
这叫疯狂
This is crazy.
你又不是小孩
You're not a child.
你有自主权
You can make your own plans.
不 如果他疯了 这种情况下
No,crazy is what house would/normally do in this situation—
他会把你的润滑剂换成强力胶
swap your lubricant with superglue.
他了解我
The man knows me.
这是他接受我们在一起的表现
this is his way of accepting us.
实际上你应该表示感动
It's actually a very touching moment.
我建议每隔一天 每隔一周末归我
I'm proposing I get every other/day and every other weekend.
星期三我有瑜伽课 那天归你
I have yoga wednesdays./You can have him then.
但是晚上11点前得让他回来
But you have to have him home by 11:00.
周末可以轮换
We can swap weekends.
星期一三 12点前
Mondays and wednesdays,and midnight.
要是12点才回 我们2点前都睡不了
If he's not home till midnight,we/won't be asleep till almost 2:00.
Wilson裁断一下
Wilson,make a ruling.
才不
No.
你们就像公园里追着转圈的狗
You two are like dogs/circling eh other in the park.
我是充满爱意说这番话的
And I say that with all/the love in the world.
你们得先互嗅屁股 龇牙示威/才能达成怪异共识
You need to sniff each other's butts,bare/your teeth,and arrive at some strange detente.
否则 只会斗得个你死我活
Otherwise,you'll end up/biting each other's eyes out.
重申 我是充满爱意说这番话的
Again,with all the love in the world.
让你先嗅我屁股吧
I'll let you sniff first.
按我说的 否则就滚出我家
Take my deal,or get out of my apartment.
按我说的 否则我就住进来啦
Take my deal,or I move in.
他在哥斯达黎加为人道主义组织工作
This guy worked for habitat/for humanity in costa rica.
还辅导残疾儿童
And coaches handicapped kids.
我们是否还要查一下其他教练有没有病?
You think we should do a/work-up on the other coaches?
他也许是太完美了
It is possible he's too perfect.
我没说他完美
I'm not saying he's perfect.
只是说他尽量做到完美
I'm saying he's trying to be.
人是这样的啊
That's what people do.
怎么?
What?
人们不会这样
That's not what people do.
人性本恶 但是人性向善 想变得更好
People usually suck,but they/want to be good,want to be nice.
House呢?
House?
有例外才证明有规律
Exception that proves the rule.
这算什么论据?
What sort of argument is that?
差劲的论据
A bad one.
也许与这有关
That might be relevant.
氢氟酸
Hydrofluoric acid.
导致他缺钙引起昏迷和味觉阻碍
Lowers his calcium,causes/the fainting and taste issue.
但解释不了和善
But not the niceness.
这样不是更好?
Wouldn't that be nice?
你就是所罗门王
You are king solomon.
下旨把他切成两半 我们都同意
If you want us to cut him/in half,we're cool with that.
我男友太懦弱 不敢自己做主
My boyfriend's too much of a wuss/to make the call for himself—
我是充满爱意说这番话的
and I mean that with all/the love in the world.
我会把其中一个得罪的/而且他们都吓唬我
I'm gonna piss off one of/them,and they both scare me.
"你的治疗方式应受谴责"
"Your treatment of/patients is reprehensible."
你在读他的表现评估?
You're reading his performance review?
我很忙
I'm busy.
护士罢工了
We have a nurses' strike.
"你滥用管理权力"
"Your management of/employees borders on abuse."
我们走吧
Let's go.
不-我想听听
No,why-- I want to hear it.
"你公开地侮辱医院高层"
"You are overtly contemptuous/of hospital hierarchy."
私下地也有
And covertly.
我想你还不知道
I suppose you didn't know about that.
"你对上级态度很不敬"
"Your attitude towards supervisory/personnel "is disrespectful,
你的言论有一大部分带有种族和性别歧视
"and a disturbingly large proportion/of your comments are racist or sexist."
这件上衣让你看起来像阿富汗妓女
That top makes you look like/an afghani prostitute.
是我评语的鲜活例证
Would be an example of that.
签字
Sign this.
- House 发现/- 等下
- House. I got the--/- it can wait.
只要你下个裁决 我就签字
I will sign,if you/will give us a ruling.
只要你对小组成员做评估/我就给你裁决
I will give you a ruling,if/you do the reviews on your team.
我很乐意继续藐视这项程序
I'd be happy to continue the/mockery of this process.
你提出的协议是?
What'd you offer him?
周三到晚上11点 周末轮流
Wednesdays till 11:00 and/alternate weekends.
周三到晚上11点归House 周末轮流
Wednesdays till 11:00/and alternate weekends.
好耶
Yes.
在猎豹酒吧周四是女士之夜
Wednesday nights are/ladies' nights at cheetah'S.
血钙正常
Calcium's normal.
哇 果然等得起
wow, It really could wait.
所有都正常
Everything's normal.
难道你以为不该么?
And you thought it wouldn't be.
他是地毯清洁工 家里尽是氢氟酸
He's a carpet cleaner. He's got/a home full of hydrofluoric acid.
不意味着他的血钙应该偏低
That doesn't mean his/calcium should be low.
本该偏低 氢氟酸使血钙变低
Yeah,it actually kinda does./Hf causes lower levels of--
变得低 不是偏低
lower,not low.
- 比正常低/- 比昨天低
- Lower than normal./- Lower than yesterday.
而昨天可以是偏高的
Yesterday might have been high.
比偏高低一点是什么?
What's lower than high?
他原本有高血钙/被氢氟酸降低到了正常水准
He actually has hypercalcemia,which/is being lowered to normal by the hf.
高血钙 味觉阻碍 昏厥能得出什么?
So what gives us elevated/calcium,bad taste,and fainting?
你想到了?
I take it you know?
召集小分队
Get the team.
带劲了
This is gonna be fun.
我又来了
Hello,again.
他们觉得你太烂好人了
These people think you are not too nice.
太好? 对什么而言?
Too nice? For what?
对上帝胡乱指点下进化而来的人生来说
For life as we know it to have/evolved without an intelligent designer.
我来证明他们错了
I'm going to prove them wrong.
你妻子很难看
Your wife is very ugly.
你走开
Get out of here.
Deb
Deb.
他只是在证明观点
He's obviously trying to prove a point.
我证明了
I think I just did.
你不是完美就是病态
You're either perfect or you're sick.
就我的经验看来 病态更有可能
In my experience,sick/is much more common.
他没生病
He's not sick.
他只是友好
He's nice.
好比用烤面包机来做早饭
Nice in the sense that your toaster/is nice for making you breakfast.
是电线线路让他这么做的
It's the only thing his/wiring will let him do.
他得的是Williams综合症
He has williams syndrome.
你的丈夫有一段基因缺失/让他没有疑心
Your husband is missing the/genes that make him suspicious.
你错了 他-
You're wrong. He's--
放心 没得救
relax,there's no cure.
他吃东西有柠檬蛋奶派味儿/时不时昏厥 还傻兮兮的
He's gonna go right on tasting lemon/meringue pie,fainting,and being a sap.
其他的症状呢?
What about the other symptoms?
他没有其他症状
He has no other symptoms.
但Williams综合症应该有
But williams does.
他的牙齿 戴着眼镜
He's got teeth,glasses.
Williams综合症使智商降低20
Williams cuts iq by 20--
他没有从事物理学科
he doesn't work in the/physics department.
除非有人在地毯上溅上一个黑洞
Except when they spill a/black hole on their carpet.
小精灵般的颜面表征呢?
Elfin appearance?
和奇宝小矮人比起来/他更像精灵弓箭手
Yeah,he's more legolas than keebler,
不过我打赌也很能吃核桃饼干
but I bet you he can still/crack off a tch of pecan sandies.
音准极佳?
Perfect pitch?
你爱唱卡拉OK吧?
You love to karaoke,right?
我很差劲
I suck.
谦虚 又是一项症状
Modest. Another symptom.
不 他确实唱得很糟
No,he really does suck.
来段颤音
Give us a warble.
你会唱雪儿吗?
You know any cher?
不会 我会面包合唱团的
No. But I know bread.
宝贝 我想要你/宝贝 我需要你
Baby,I'm-a want you/baby,I'm-a need you
宁愿受伤 我也只想着你
you're the only one I/care enough to hurt about
怎么了?
What's the matter?
他中风了
He's stroking.
来得不算早
Not a moment too soon.
你错了
you were wrong.
为什么人们总乐滋滋地说这句话
Why do people say/that with such pleasure?
这挺让人伤心的
It's very hurtful,you know.
病人将继续友善下去
it means the patient/gets to keep being nice.
这让你不爽了?
Why does that offend you?
是他说话的语气
It's the way he said it.
他不是松了口气 他很兴奋
He wasn't relieved,he was excited.
他也错了
He was also wrong.
瞧我说得就不带幸灾乐祸的情绪
And I say that with no sense of pleasure.
病人测出不是Williams症
patient tested negative for williams,
说明中风和别的症状不是由--
which means the stroke/and everything else wasn't caused—
你行为友善 但有时过于投入
you have a friendly demeanor,but/you sometimes get too involved.
和同事和病人都相处得很好
You relate well to your/peers and patients.
你完成工作有效率
And you complete tasks/in a timely manner.
请签字
Please sign.
你又搞什么?
What the hell was that?
我得给你们每个人都写表现评估
I have to give each of/you performance reviews.
还有很多的病能造成衰弱及性情和善
Plenty of other conditions can/cause debilitating niceness.
这对他能有帮助吗?
How is that supposed to help him?
我不知道
I don't know.
这对Wilson又有什么帮助?
How's it supposed to help Wilson?
把日期和Wilson的名字划掉/填上你的名字
Cross out Wilson's name and the/date,and then fill in your own name.
评估的目的是给人建议 以助提高
the point of a review is/to give feedback to help.
有可能是神经性梅毒
I'm thinking neurosyphilis.
不用造影剂的话/核磁共振上看不出来
Wouldn't show up on the/mri without contrast.
我去做检查
I'll go run the tests.
他不认为是梅毒/但还是跑着去做检查
He doesn't think it's syphilis,but/he's gonna go run those tests anyway.
因为他不知道
Because he doesn't know.
这是我们进行化验的原因
That's why we do tests.
因为他是个懦夫
Because he's a wimp.
因为他怕你
Because he's afraid of you.
你想我叫他别怕我?
You want me to intimate/him into not being afraid?
我还真不知怎么做呢
Not sure I know how to do that.
工作评估有效果 人们得听这些评价/得从中学到点什么
Reviews make a difference. People/have to listen,so they have to learn.
半年才教育一次狗不许在垫子上撒尿/可没啥意义
I don't think that the right time to tell/the dog not to pee on the rug is semi-annually.
你不想做这些文书工作
You don't want to do the paperwork.
我是为热带雨林着想
I am concerned about the rainforest.
我来做
I'll do it.
我知道你会的
I know.
我没有梅毒
I don't have syphilis.
你没法知道
You don't know.
能有几种途径染上那个?
How many ways are there to get it?
你可以知道自己跟谁上过床/但没法知道她--
You can know who you had sex/with. You can't know who she--
我知道
I do.
没法确定
Not for sure.
简直是浪费时间
It's a waste of time.
我已经中风一次了
I had a stroke.
你们不能继续再浪费时间了
You can't keep wasting time.
我们加入维和部队时检测过
We were tested for the peace corps.
那是十年前
Ten years ago.
你又没有每时每刻都跟你妻子在一起
You haven't been with your/wife every minute of every day.
你觉得我很天真对吗?
You think I'm naive,don't you?
我觉得你--是天真
I think you're--yeah.
我了解我的妻子
I know my wife.
她并非完人
She's not perfect.
我也不是
I'm not perfect.
但她爱我
But she loves me.
她一直都爱我
And she's always loved me.
每时每刻
Every minute,every day.
你们迟到十五分钟了
You're 15 minutes late.
你听到了那个好消息吗?
Have you heard the good news?
Miley Cyrus在Spectrum体育馆的演唱会/加演第三场?
Miley cyrus is playing a/third night at the spectrum?
幸福变成了可能
Happiness is possible.
而且不仅仅在此生 还有来世--
And not just in this life,/but in the next--
哦 你是推销宗教的啊
oh,you're selling religion.
抱歉 昨天已经买了点伊斯兰教
I'm sorry,I bought some islam yesterday.
那是照耀你的光辉给你的启示
Well,it's where your light shows/signs before mending--
祝您有个美妙的傍晚
have a good evening.
- 你们迟到了/- 十五分钟而已
- You're late./- 15 minutes.
十六分钟 而且是我的十六分钟
16 minutes,my 16 minutes.
那你多留他十六分钟好了
So keep him an extra 16 minutes.
你听到了吗? 她根本不在乎
You hear that? She doesn't care.
你们就是玩玩迷你高尔夫罢了/能有多大关系?
You're going mini-golfing./What's it matter?
难道还有开球时间限制不成?
You got a tee off time?
关系重大 因为关系多重大不该你说了算
It matters because you don't/get to decide what matters.
是我的错 我得冲个凉
It was my fault. I had to take a shower.
还是我的错
Which was my fault.
我还得去拉屎
I had to take a dump.
你走之前还有啥我不必知道的事儿要说?
Anything else I don't need/to know before you leave?
游乐时间玩得开心点
Have fun on your play date.
你有妈咪的电话对吗?
You've got mommy's numbers,right?
爹地要先喝一杯
Daddy needs a drink.
我在想 要是我们别多管那个善良问题--
I was thinking,if we/discount the niceness issue--
坐吧
sit down.
我想可能是心脏缺陷
I think it's a heart defect.
超声波上没啥不正常
Nothing on the echo.
可能是卵圆孔未闭
Could bea patent foramen ovale.
可以解释中风和昏厥
It explains the stroke,and the syncope,
卵圆孔未闭在常规超声心动图中不会显示
and a pfo wouldn't show/up on a routine echo.
我去做个心脏超声造影
I'm gonna do a bubble test.
有时间吗?
You got a minute first?
当然
Sure.
我认为你在困境下显示出非凡的能力
I think you've shown remarkable/strength in a difficult situation.
你来写我的表现评估?
Are you giving me a performance review?
评语很优秀
A good one.
我去做心脏超声造影
I'm gonna do a bubble test.
他入院时抽的血样够做个梅毒血清测试
there was enough blood left over from/his admission work-up to run the vdrl.
你怀疑你的病人
You doubted your patient.
不 我怎么想不重要
No,what I thought didn't matter.
House说了 如果不先排除神经性梅毒/就不让我们继续
House said he wouldn't let us go/on until we ruled out neurosyphilis.
不是神经性梅毒 是卵圆孔未闭
It's not neurosyphilis;it's a pfo.
就是神经性梅毒
It's neurosyphilis.
检测结果是阳性
The tests were positive.
总是老生常谈
it's always the same conversation.
他们告诉你肯定是你弄错了
They tell you you must be mistaken,
所以我总是把测试做两遍
which is why I always/run the tests twice,
然后他们就指责自己的伴侣
and then they blame the other guy,
要他们无辜的话 这样就说得通
which makes sense if they're innocent,
但很明显 一半的人并不无辜
but obviously,half of 'em aren't.
他们没明白自己已经被揭穿了
They don't seem to/get that they're busted.
被科学证明了
Scientifically proven.
除非你的配偶也出轨
Unless your spouse cheated too.
正是如此 那种情况下你最希望的/就是这样
Exactly. That's what you're/praying for in that moment.
她也出轨了
That she cheated too.
如果她不想杀了你 你便能知道她也出轨了
And then if she doesn't/kill you,you know that she did.
你知道她背叛了你
You know she betrayed you.
然后 你意识到这样更糟
And then,you realize that/that sucks worse.
测试结果肯定错了
The test must be wrong.
我做了两遍
I ran it twice.
不是说那个测试
Not that test.
是我十年前做的那个
The one I took ten years ago.
要不还有怎么解释?
What other explanation is there?
他完全想不到还有其它可能性
He really sees no other possibility.
你有外遇吗?
Did you have an affair?
没有
No.
那你为什么不对他发火?
Then why aren't you angry with him?
- 你认识老好人吗?/- 没有
- You ever know anybody who's just too nice?/- No.
很讨人厌--然后你意识到讨厌的原因是/他们让你看到自己的缺点
It's annoying--then you realize it's annoying/because they remind you of what you are not.
你永远不可能跟他们一样好
That you'll never be as good as they are.
然后你会想 我为什么不能?
And then you think,why can't I?
你还没意识到/那个你嘲弄的傻瓜就让你变成了更好的人
And before you know it,that naive idiot you/laughed at has made you a better person.
你真觉得我这些年是爱上了个病症?
You really think I've been in/love all these years with a symptom?
要是梅毒造成了大脑损伤/而损伤引起人格变化
If syphilis caused lesions in his brain,and/the lesions caused personality changes,
等他情况好转后/你可能会注意到他的变化
you may notice a change in/him as his condition improves.
我了解我丈夫
I know my husband.
他不会变的
He's not gonna change.
你最好也检查一下
You should get yourself tested.
正态分布理论就是如此
So much for the bell curve.
凭什么House是个混蛋不是病态/而人太好了就是病呢?
How can House be an ass without it being an/illness,but niceness is a biological crime?
你有五块钱吗?
You got five bucks?
有
Uh,yeah.
人好就让你损失了五块钱
Niceness just cost you five bucks.
而混蛋一般都能得益
Being an ass generally turns a profit.
Kutner 你能让我们俩单独待着吗?
Kutner,could you excuse us?
我得做Taub的评估
I need to do taub's review.
你留下来
You can stay.
我想这私底下进行比较好
I think it would be better if/this was done privately.
根本不可能真做评估
This isn't gonna be done.
你们这是怎么了?/我以前也给过你们建议啊
What is it with you guys?/I've given you advice before.
不是以我们上司的身份
Not as our boss.
区别在哪儿? 建议就是建议
What's the difference? Advice is advice.
成
Fair enough.
我先说
I'll go first.
你表现出极度的自信 让我很不爽
You demonstrate a great air of/confidence,which is really pissing me off.
- House授权我--/- 你认识他多久了? 他在利用你
- House authorized me--/- how long have you known him? He's using you.
我主动提出的 因为我知道他肯定不会
I volunteered because I knew he wouldn'T.
他根本不在乎那些文书工作
He could care less about the paperwork.
他利用你 整你
He's using you to screw with you.
他知道这会让我们不爽
He knows it'll annoy us.
我们会跟你对着干 迫使你看清现实
We'll stand up to you,which will/force you to confront the fact
虽然你以为自己比我们等级高
that even though you/think you're our superior,
你其实跟我们一样
you're no different from us.
他给你权威是让你知道自己的位置
He gave you authority/to keep you in your place.
是真的
It's true.
谢了
Thanks.
不是说他 他刚说什么了?
Not him,what'd he say?
没什么 你说什么是真的?
Nothing,what's true?
这人肯定有问题
There's something wrong with this guy,
就说明House肯定有问题
it means there's/something wrong with House.
你想把我灌醉吗?
Are you trying to get me drunk?
几点了?
What time is it?
10:30
10:30.
她会杀了你的
She'll kill you.
我会在熄灯前把你弄回家的
I'll get you home before lights out.
很好 那她就会杀了我
Great. Then she'll kill me.
如果我--如果我再喝醉点就会--
If I get--if I get any/more drunk,then I'm--
它...就可能罢工
it...might not work.
如果你 呃 明白我的意思
If you,uh,know what I mean.
真的?
Really?
你有没有意识到/你的某位前妻跟我说起过
You'd think that one or more of your/ex-wives would have mentioned that to me.
她们连这个都告诉你?
They told you?
等一下
Wait.
你为什么想要Amber生气?
Why do you want to get amber angry?
因为我是你的朋友
Because I'm your friend.
不 不 不 你说过你同意了的
No,no,no. You said you approved,
你说你会走正道
you said you were taking-the high road.
持续多久? 只到第一个出口?
For how long,the first exit?
你好 感谢你让我不用再听滥好人罗嗦
Hello,and thank you for saving me/from being righteoused to death.
病人在吐血
patient's vomiting blood.
- 吐血可能说明--/- 别写在白板上
- Hematemesis could indicate--/- don't put it on the board.
你觉得这不是个症状?
You don't think it's a symptom?
笔是我的
I think it's my marker.
他有梅毒 然后呢?
he has syph. And what?
梅毒 可能导致咳血
And syph,it can cause hematemesis.
有人不同意
not everyone agrees.
你--你怎么知道—
How--how could you—
因为如果你们都觉得就是梅毒
because if you all/thought it was just syph,
就不会大半夜吵醒我了
you wouldn't have woken me/upin the middle of the night.
要只是梅毒 他应该不会恶化
If it was just syph,he/wouldn't be getting worse.
我们已经上了青霉素
He's already on penicillin.
出血有可能是肝脏损伤
bleeding's probably from liver damage,
可能是清洁剂里面的乙醇或青霉素引起的
probably caused by ethanol in/the cleansers or the penicillin.
比我想听到的多了两种可能
Two more probablys than I like to hear.
肝脏和血清测试得花一天
Liver tests and serologies are/gonna take a full day.
准确说是一整晚
Full night,actually.
病人可能撑不到早午饭
guy not might make it to brunch.
是的 我知道你喝醉了会如何
Yes,I knew about your issue with alcohol.
是的 我故意把你灌醉/好在你和Amber间煽风点火
Yes,I intentionally got you drunk to/provoke an argument between you and amber.
我这么干的原因则是个有趣的问题
Why I would do such a thing/is an interesting question.
更有趣的是 你明明跟我一样清楚后果
What's more interesting is/that you knew as much as I did
却还一杯杯狂灌
and you're the one who's/pouring down the drinks.
为什么?
Why?
因为我以为我在跟朋友一起找乐子
Because I thought I was/out having fun with a friend.
不知道这些酒还有别的含义
I didn't know the drinks had subtext.
我得回家了
I gotta get home.
谷氨酰转肽酶正常
Ggt's normal.
排除了酒精
Rules out alcohol.
那血清蛋白的?
How about serum protein?
阳性
It's positive.
只能说明他有蛋白
Kinda assumed he had protein.
关键在于他有多少数量的蛋白
It's how much protein/he has we care about.
梅毒是阳性
It's positive for syphilis.
要我给你做个评估吗?
You mind if I give/you a performance review?
不是病人的
Not the patient.
House
House.
他得了梅毒
He has syphilis.
怎么了?
what happened?
每次当我搜寻我的灵魂时...
every time I searched my soul...
我都找到了Anna
I found anna.
那你打算告诉Marie吗?
are you gonna tell marie?
我必须告诉她
I have to.
那会毁了她的
it will destroy her.
会比爱上个不会回应她的人更惨吗?
could it be any worse on her than/loving somebody who can't love them back?
咋了?
Yes?
你最好把电视关了
You might want to turn off the tv.
我能同时应付多重任务
I'm multi-tasking.
还在对付我的报税单
Also doing my taxes.
和Cuddy
And Cuddy.
你们有什么发现?
What'd you find out?
病人得了肝炎
The patient has hepatitis.
你们没有用病毒性肝炎这个词/我想这不是另一例性病了
I assume from your omission of the word/'viral' before the hep that it's not another std.
用类固醇 测结节病/免得他的肝损伤变成肝坏死
Put him on steroids and test him for sarcoid/before the liver failure becomes liver failed.
这事儿我们得一起面对
We're all doing this.
还有别的?
There's more?
你有梅毒
You have syphilis.
不 我没有
No,I don't.
- 我们有人在实验室里找到了瓶你的血样/- 谁找到的?
- One of us found a vial of your blood in the lab--/- which one of you?
可以治疗的
It's treatable
给你开了份药
we filled a prescription.
你没事吧?
You okay?
这是他变成现在这样子的原因
So this is why he is who he is.
不好说
We don't know.
就是这样
we know.
不只是巧合
It's not just a coincidence.
Wilson说他一直是个混蛋
Wilson says he's always been a jerk.
但他变得更混蛋了
But he got worse.
腿出问题之后
After his leg.
腿出问题是个巧合
The leg was a coincidence.
你跟他上过床没?
Did you sleep with him?
会怎么样?
So what's gonna happen?
会有什么改变?
What's gonna change?
也许他不会那么混蛋
Maybe he'll be less of a jerk.
医术也没那么高明了
Or less of a doctor.
得先是个混蛋才能是好医生?
You gotta be a jerk to be a good doctor?
我不知道 也许House是的
I don't know. Maybe house does.
你为什么不回答我?
Why aren't you answering me?
因为那跟他们无关
Because it's none of their business.
也与你无关
It's none of your business.
这是性病 就跟我有关了
I think the std makes it my business.
人类是很复杂的
Humans are complicated.
人类很简单
Humans are simple.
数以万计的小事件让我们成为现在这样
a million different/things make us who we are.
改变其中一个 就可能改变一切
You change one,you change everything.
要是莫扎特身体健康 对打球感兴趣/就没有魔笛了
If mozart was better adjusted,decides to play/catch one day,maybe there's no magic flute.
你跟他上床了对吗?
You did,didn't you?
我有事必须告诉你
There's something I need to tell you.
你把他醉醺醺地还给我
you returned him drunk.
准时
On time.
喝醉了
Drunk.
准时 不许再回嘴
On time. No tag backs.
限定时间的目的是给我时间
The purpose of the/time was to give me time.
那你们没做成爱咯?
So you didn't have sex?
我喜欢性爱
I like sex.
那你今晚就能得到它了
Then you can have it tonight.
拉字至上今晚播
The L word is on.
你没权决定什么关系重大
You don't get to decide what matters.
要么你是真心担忧我会让他痛苦不堪
Either you're genuinely afraid/I'm gonna make him miserable,
要么你是担心我会让他快乐
or you're afraid I'm/gonna make him happy,
要么你就是没法让自己不捣乱—
or you simply can't stop screwing/with anything that moves—
但这不重要 因为无论原因如何/你只会变本加厉
it doesn't really matter because/whatever the reason,you'll only get worse.
直到我要么跟Wilson分手/要么不让你见他
Until either I stop/seeing Wilson,or I stop you.
你觉得我会选哪样?
What do you think I'm gonna choose?
你要是中止我们的约定/可不能为中东带来和平
If you terminate the agreement,it's/not gonna bring peace in the mideast.
我没有中止约定
I'm not terminating the agreement.
我在修正约定
I'm amending the agreement.
我要加上惩罚条款
I'm adding penalty clauses.
好啊
Fine.
谁要违反了就砍手指
Whoever violates it gets/their finger cut off.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
我也是
So am I.
要想人们能安全驾驶
You want people to drive safer,
就把安全气囊拆了/弄把大砍刀正对着他们的脖子
take out the airbags and attach/a machete pointing at their neck.
没人敢开车时速超过3英里
No one will drive over/three miles per hour.
- 我不砍--/- 我们再讨论
- I'm not cutting--/- we'll figure it out.
用你的时间
On your time.
你知道她精神不正常吧?
You know she's certifiable,right?
我桌子里有表格
I got the forms in my desk.
她哪里错了?
Where is she wrong?
你打算告诉我什么?
What were you gonna tell me?
没什么
Nothing.
你在惩罚我?
You're punishing me?
我得私下告诉你件事
I needed to tell you something privately.
我不会告诉她的
I'm not gonna tell her.
你会的
You'll tell her.
她是你女朋友
She's your girlfriend.
你应该告诉她
You should tell her.
但你是我的朋友
You're my friend.
那不是一回事
It's not the same.
别闷闷不乐
Don't sulk.
我哪儿错了?
Where am I wrong?
你的管理风格效率极低
your management style/is counterproductive.
你给我权利监管全组/只为了让他们有机会—
You gave me authority over the/team,just so they could undercut—
批评花柳病人?
critiquing the clap-addled?
真不像话
That's sort of tasteless.
我不想等到你的生殖器没问题了再说
I didn't feel like waiting until/your genitals cleared up.
你得赋予我正式权利
You need to formalize my/authority over the team.
不
No,I don't.
你觉得我不合格?
You don't think I'm qualified?
和那三个比?
Compared to those three?
Cuddy未经你同意就聘任我/你要惩罚她?
You wanna punish Cuddy for/hiring me without--
我喜欢Cuddy 喜欢她身上某些部分
I like Cuddy. I like parts of her.
你想通过摧毁我 来摧毁整个小组?
You wanna crush the team by crushing me?
我想赋予他们力量
I want to empower them.
他们理应尊重你
Those three idiots need to respect you.
应该尊重你
They should respect you.
他们应该怕你
They should be afraid of you.
所以我得羞辱你
So I have to humiliate you.
因为医疗小组如果怕你/他们就不会质疑你
'Cause if the team fears/you,they won't question you;
不质疑 就想不出答案
if they don't question/you,they won't get any answers;
想不出答案 他们就没用了
if they don't get any/answers,they're useless.
嘲弄我能救得性命?
Mocking me saves lives?
医院没准那天会为你塑一尊雕像
The hospital will probably build/you a statue one day.
雕像背后挂幅"踹我一脚"的标语
You know,with a "kick/me" sign on the back.
这么想的话 我越是嘲弄你/说明我越看重你
So when you think about it,the more I mock/you, the more it shows I have respect for you.
编这堆废话不过是因为你乐衷于羞辱我
Or you made up that B.S./Because you like humiliating me.
也有这可能
Wouldn't rule that out completely.
在忙?
You busy?
快好了
Almost done.
记住 兔子绕着树跑 然后一头跳进坑里
Uh,so just remember,the rabbit goes/around the tree and jumps down the hole.
不是结节病
Negative for sarcoidosis.
测试所有可能的病
Run him for everything you can think of.
钩端螺旋体病 血吸虫 血液病/或是不为人知的第四个马克思兄弟
Lepto,schisto,hemo,and the fourth/marx brother nobody ever heard of.
死女人!
You bitch!
我去端午饭 你睡着了
I just went to get us/some lunch,you were asleep.
你动了我的书
You moved my book.
Jeff 冷静点
Jeff. Calm down.
是药的缘故
It's just the drugs.
药不会动我的书
The drugs didn't/move my book--
Jeff?
jeff?
我丈夫心脏病发作了 谁来帮帮我?
My husband's having a heart/attack-- can somebody help me,please?
来人帮忙!
Somebody help me,please!
她救了他的命
She saved his life.
她破坏了罢工
Or she scabbed.
看你从哪个角度看
Depends on your point of view.
大家怎么看?
So what do we think?
新的症状?
New symptom?
纯粹就是个打老婆的人?
Or just a wife beater?
嘿
Hey.
轮到你使这了
Time for you to/take this baby for a spin.
我们给他用强的松 来治疗肝脏
We,uh,loaded him full of/prednisone to try to fix the liver.
好消息 他可供衰竭的脏器不多了
Good news is,he's running/out of organs to fail.
强的松这种内固醇药物可致暴躁/过度紧张
Prednisone could cause 'roid rage,which/could cause hypertension,which results—
6个小时后内显现固醇药物副作用?
'roid rage after six hours?
照这个速度 天黑前 他就会把我们都吃了
At that rate,by sundown,he'll/have eaten most of us.
仍可能是青霉素
Uh,it still could be penicillin.
过敏反应
Allergic reaction.
肝脏烧坏了 会让他暴怒?
How does a fried/liver put him into a rage?
烧的不是肝脏 而是梅毒
It's not frying his/liver,it's frying hisyphilis.
青霉素起作用了
The penicillin's working.
真正的病人浮出水面
The real patient is emerging,
梅毒能防止家庭暴力
so syphilis prevents domestic violence.
怪不得我倍受女性青睐
I'm gonna be more/attractive to the ladies.
在测试梅毒之前 我本要做心脏测试-
I was gonna test for a heart/issue before the syphilis.
卵圆孔未闭能解释心脏病发作/减少了流向大脑的血液 引发暴怒
Pfo could explain the heart attack and reduced/blood flow to the brain could explain the rage.
都是好主意
Well,all good ideas.
来投票
Okay,let's take a vote.
有谁认为是固醇引起的?
How many think it's the 'roids talking?
谁投给青霉素?
And who's for the penicillin?
那她说的呢?
And how about whatever she said?
有人没有举手
Someone hasn't raised their hand.
我选哪个有什么要紧?
Whatever I decide?
你陷害我
You're setting me up.
我为什么要陷害你?
Why would I do that?
卵圆孔未闭
Pfo.
卵圆孔未闭胜出
The pfos have it.
我希望心脏超声造影检查出阳性
I just hope the bubble test is positive.
不然就没好好先生了
Or it's no more Mr. nice guy.
给凡高用螯合治疗
We gave van gogh chelation therapy.
把天才画家变成了粉刷匠
Turned him into a house painter.
也许不是
maybe not.
也许我们是给希特勒用利他林
Maybe we just put Hitler on ritalin.
你把House比作希特勒?
Are you comparing House to Hitler?
天
Oh god.
就算我不认为House是希特勒/也不代表我和他睡过
Just because I don't think he's/Hitler doesn't mean I slept with him.
不是比希特勒好的人 我就得跟他睡
I don't sleep with/everyone who's better than Hitler.
也许Taub对
Maybe taub is right.
这不挺好
Maybe this is good.
这不好
This is not good.
他尊重我们的意见 他自我嘲讽/他讲文明 懂得分享
Well,he respected our opinions,he/mockedhimself,he was civil,he shared.
他不在乎了
He didn't care.
他从不在乎
He never cares.
他都不投票
He didn't vote.
从来他只关心一件事
He always cared about one thing.
解决疑难
Solving the puzzle.
可他游离在诊断外
But he was irrelevant to that diagnosis.
没有自己的意见
He had no opinion of his own.
他现在什么都不在乎了
He now cares about nothing.
没别的选择 得治疗他
You had no choice;you had to treat him.
木已成舟
What's done is done.
我非得告诉你不可 我憋不住了
You know that thing I was gonna/tell you,I gotta tell you.
我得告诉谁
I gotta tell someone.
你发誓不告诉蛇蝎女
You've got to swear not to tell C.B.
随便你
Whatever.
这不是发誓 是耸肩
Well,that's not/swearing,that's shrugging.
这可是发誓的反义
It's actually the opposite of swearing.
我不告诉Amber
I won't tell amber.
我小组认为我得了梅毒
My team thinks that I have syphilis.
你得了么?
Do you?
还没呢
Not yet.
他们为什么认为你得了?
Why do they think you do?
我知道他们能拿到我的一份旧血液样本
Because I knew that they had/access to an old blood sample,
我还料到他们总会拿去测测的
and I knew they'd test/it sometime for something.
你为什么要调换样本?/你怕他们发现什么?
Why would you swap your blood?/What are you afraid they'll find?
别扯 你漏掉了重点
Shut up,you're missing the point.
他们以为我在服用青霉素
Now,they think that I'm on penicillin.
这个恶作剧的笑点我还没抓到
Is this some clever practical/joke that I'm not aware of?
当我病情好转了 我性情也变好了
And as I get better,I get nicer.
太高明了
That's brilliant.
Foreman以为我重视他的观点
Foreman thinks I actually/value his opinion.
还好他投了卵圆孔未闭/不然我得手舞足蹈了
Thank god he said pfo,or/I'd have had to do some dancing.
有空打保龄球吗?
You got time for bowling?
去吧 现在是上班时间
Come on,it's work hours.
我去拿鞋
I'll get my shoes.
- 我们不用谈论/- 不用
- So we don't need to talk about--/- no.
- 你会继续捣乱/- 会
- You're gonna keep screwing--/- yeah.
你可以继续谈 我们还是本来那样
You're gonna keep talking about/it. We are who we are.
我去拿鞋
I'll get my shoes.
心脏看得清楚了
Okay,got a good view of the heart.
我们减少给House的药物剂量如何?
What if we lower house's dosage?
稳定住他就好 不恶化 也不改善
Maybe stabilize him,he doesn't/get worse,he doesn't get better.
分寸不好把握
Quite the line to walk.
一旦犯错 他就会死于神经性梅毒
If we're wrong, he dies of neurosyphilis.
如果不这么做 别的人会死
If we don't,other people die.
别人不是我们老板
Other people who aren't our boss.
是人
People.
这不好 他有天赋才能
This sucks. The guy had a gift.
我会害死--
I'd kill--
- 你来--/- House没得梅毒
- hi,what--/- house doesn't have syphilis.
他调换了血液样本
He switched the blood samples.
你怎么知道?
How do you know that?
House告诉Wilson
House told Wilson.
我想破坏House的好戏
I wanted to ruin house's day.
再会
See ya.
- 我们真是蠢蛋/- 我们不蠢
- We're idiots./- We're not idiots.
测试的血液样本确实是梅毒阳性
Positive blood test/means positive blood test.
明显他没有
Apparently not.
看到了 瞧瞧他们
There they are,let's see if they--
你去哪儿? 还没完呢
uh,what are you doing? We're not done.
他没得梅毒
He doesn't have syphilis.
我知道
I know.
病人测试出梅毒阳性
patient tested positive/for syphilis,right?
你是来温故而知新么?
Is this some sort of recap?
但为什么他测试出梅毒阳性?
But why did he test/positive for syphilis?
噢 这我知道
Oh,I know this.
要么一 他得了梅毒
Either,one: He has syphilis--
我正要说这个
I was gonna say that.
二 两次测试都检查错了/三 他把别人的血液给我们
Or two: The test was wrong twice,or/three,he gave us someone else's blood.
谁说的?
Who?
Amber
Amber.
别在我面前晃悠你傻笑的脸
Get that idiotic smile out of my face.
我要去杀人了
I gotta go on a killing spree.
还有四 他得了某种病 会测试出梅毒阳性
Or,four,he has something/that tests positive for syphilis.
不是南美洲锥虫病
It's not chagas.
他婚前在哥斯达黎加工作过
He worked in costa/rica before he was married.
就那两鸟人 还是你也想送死
Is two a spree,/or do I have to kill you too?
锥虫病无法解释过度和蔼
Chagas wouldn't explain the niceness.
我听说过有些偏远部落确实特别善良
I've heard of remote tribes that/actually practice acts of kindness.
可能锥虫病导致了脑炎
Or the chagas caused encephalitis.
核磁共振没有显示出
The mri showed no sign--
我们给他用了类固醇药物后/抑制了免疫系统
until we started him on/steroids,compromised the immune system,
感染飙升了
and let the infection flare up.
我又做了一次核磁共振
I did another one.
不是很明显
It's not much.
但足以说明了
It's plenty.
你从我没得梅毒想到的?
You figured this out because/I don't have syphilis?
该死
Damn.
本该我揭开谜团
That should have been my epiphany.
有好消息 也有坏消息
Good news,bad news.
好消息是我们查出你得到了什么病/能治 你能活下去
Good news is we know what you/have,it's treatable,you're gonna live.
真的?
Really?
坏消息是?
What's the bad news?
治疗要吃很多很多药
The cure is a grueling course of pills.
好比一个月要花去一天时间
It's like one a day for a month.
你这是在让我发笑
Now you're just trying to make me laugh.
让你笑可不是桩难题
Yeah,like that's a challenge.
你得了锥虫病
You have chagas disease.
是种寄生虫
It's a parasite.
十年来没有表现出症状
It's been asymptomatic for ten years.
非也 你的脑子肿胀了 虽不是很明显
Not quite. Your brain's been/swollen--not enough to see,
但足以改变你的性情
but enough to alter your personality.
又绕回来了
Now we're back to that.
你冲你嚷嚷了
He screamed at you.
你不认为他会改变?
You don't think he could change?
那是药物的缘故
That was because of the drugs.
你认为药物比寄生虫还强大?
So you think drugs are/more powerful than parasites?
我们开给你治疗寄生虫的药物--
I mean,the ones we're gonna give you/to treat the parasites obviously are—
我坚持我的观点
I standby the principle.
我不担心
I'm not worried.
我也不担心
Neither am I.
我也不
因为我不关心
But that's because I don't care.
评估?
Reviews?
我注意到 有些时候
It was brought to my/attention that on occasion,
我不太尊重医院的规章制度
I am not respectful/of hospital hierarchy.
正确用语是"鄙视"
The word was "contemptuous."
用词恰当 有深度
Well-phrased,thoughtful.
用词一模一样
Identically phrased.
都是一样的
These are all the same.
因为 说到底 人都是一样的
Because,underneath it/all,we are all the same.
Foreman拒绝写他自己的
And foreman refused to type his up.
算是超出我的预期了
Well,it's more than I expected.
还附送一份
There's an extra one in there.
"你给予病人的治疗不存在/因为你不是医生 你是行政人员"
"Your treatment of patients is non-existent because/you're not a doctor,you're an administrator."
Foreman提醒我 写这些会有帮助
Foreman convinced me that/these could be helpful.
"你对员工的管理: 算了 面对现实吧/他们还在外边举着标语呢"
"Your management of employees is,well,let's/face it,they're outside carrying signs."
罢工结束了
The strike ended.
护士已经回来工作两个轮班了
The nurses have been back/for two shifts already.
你觉得我会留意么
You'd think I'd have noticed.
他们到底干些什么?
What exactly did they do around here?
"你想让员工尊敬你/但你的眼睛告诉我们-"
"You act like employees "should fear/and respect you,but your eyes tell us—
"但你的眼睛什么都没说/因为我们光顾看你的胸部了"
"but your eyes tell us nothing/"because we're looking at our boobs,
"说明你急切滴想要有人上你"
"which tell us that you're desperate/"to have someone jump on you
"并想有人嘟囔着告诉你 他们爱你"
and tell you they love you "one/grunted syllable at a time. "
你想要的 你逃避
What you want,you run away from.
你需要的 你不自知
"What you need,"you don't have a clue.
你的成就让你自豪
"What you've/accomplished,makes you proud.
但你还是很可悲
But you're still miserable."
请签字
Please sign.
今天我接到Amber的电话
I got a call from amber today.
说你违反了协议
Says there's been a/violation of your contract.
你在她的时间里见Wilson
You've been seeing Wilson on her time.
她也违反了保密条款
She breached confidentiality.
睁一只眼闭一只眼吧 长官
You can let it slide,officer.
我们打平
We're even.
是的
Yes,you are.
你们都要被剁掉手指
You're both losing fingers.
瞧我找来什么
Look what I found.
好极了
Nice.
医生说你大概明天就能回家了
They think you might be/able to come home tomorrow.
真的? 太好了
Oh,yeah? That's good.
怎么了?
What's the matter?
番茄酱
The ketchup.
有些不对劲
There's something wrong with that.
味道不错啊
Tastes fine.
还有什么?
Anything else?
别的都好极了
Everything else is great.
我只是--
I'm just--I don't know.
我不再喜欢番茄酱了
I guess I don't like ketchup anymore.
也许还有什么别的 我也不喜欢了
Wonder what else I don't like.
翻身
roll over.
这个惩罚还不够重
we need a tougher punishment.
你到便便这边来
Come over to the poopy side.
你俩周五晚上去哪儿?
where are you two going friday night?
去l'auberge吃晚餐
Dinner at l'auberge.
你说谎
you're lying.
我当然是骗你的
Of course I am.